You guys really need to stop this nonsense.
Today is the Tokyo Metropolis League.
The first game for the B-Team.
What's with you all this week?
This negativity is really killing your team's morale.
Honestly, you're not competing against some world-class opponent out here.
This should be low-hanging fruit, but we're barely going to get by.
And why?
Have you noticed that ever since that whole thing went down with Asari, the rest of the first years are feeling it too?
I mean, he's like criminal crazy man. I didn't think he'd be that pissed.
It's like all his hair fell out when they made Ashito a starter.
You stole their spot!
Talk about nuts. But I admit I'm obsessed with what he said.
Yeah, I feel you, bro. This sucks. How are we supposed to play at our best feeling like this?
And right now you're wondering, why were Kurada and Asari mad at you?
Find the answer to that question.
If you can't do that, I won't field you in a match for the next three months.
So act as if your life depends on it.
I'm afraid I don't have the answers yet, coach. Sorry. My only priority right now is this game.
Okay, dry your eyes. I told you I'll be home at some point.
When? How am I supposed to know that? But I'll see you then. You just don't stop, do you? What are you, my mother now?
Hey, old man! Sorry! Manager Fukuda?
Yeah? What do you want?
Is that... Hana?
Yeah. That's weird. How'd you know? Wait a minute. You're not seeing her, are you?
Can you hold up your receiver really quick? My receiver? You mean my cell phone?
Hey! I just wanna say I'm doing your meal plan. And? I'm off to play in my first match and they made me a starter, isn't that cool?
Yeah! My official debut is as the reincarnation of Farence Puskas!
Ha ha ha ha ha ha!
So if you wanna come cheer for me, you can. That's all.
Uh... Ashito. You think you can win? How do you feel?
I've never had to think this much about a game before. But we'll win.
Yeah? How do you figure?
Cause I'm gonna score for us.
I love to be the one to point out the obvious, but... Soccer is what we call a team sport. You can't do anything alone.
That's what makes it fun. That's what it's all about.
What the? Is Spurion Youth Team B?
B? No way! There can't be two teams! What am I supposed to do? I was told to photograph the future national team! How do I know which one that is if the teams are split in two? Mr. Sekio is going to kill me!
Let's go, Sekio! Let's go, Sekio!
Hmm, so this is the opponent's side. No flashy cheer teams, like at high school level. And no one following, so they're easy to spot, which is cool. So they must be...
Yep, called it!
Oh, by the way, did you mean what you said earlier? Are there actually good players on this team? Do you just know a lot about a Spurion, or what?
Uh, okay. Sorry, you seemed like a nice person who might have some answers. But we all know looks can be deceiving.
I get that they're the B team, but aren't they supposed to be elite players? They kind of low.
Yeah, what a joke.
The hell, Takashima? What is your problem? I was trying to pass it to the front, dude!
Seriously? No one's coming to follow up?
Left side, watch out!
How did every single one of you what sound like that?
Nice goal!
Bunch of idiots!
35 minutes into the first half? It's zero to three?
What was that besides pathetic? We may be the B team, but we are still wearing the Asperion uniform. Step it up!
We did everything we were supposed to.
Please enlighten me. When you use the pronoun, we, who exactly are you referring to, Aseri?
Everyone in this room was off their game today, including you, Princess, so stop being so desperate to blame the tryout players!
That's not what I'm doing. Cut it out!
I'm so disappointed in all of you. You brought your childish issues from practice right into the game.
It's humiliating to see you be so careless and give up three goals. You're wasting your talent by acting like babies!
Didn't you come here because you want to be professional players?
There was not one hair on your skin that could claim an atom of professionalism.
Maybe because I still have no clue how to figure out this stupid assignment.
First half, I tried defense and that was frickin' boring.
I also tried less dribbling and more passing so that no one would cry about not touching the ball.
Even though I was bored to tears. I'm so over the sharing as caring baby soccer.
Well, that's the price to pay when you're a genius. You can do anything and everything. They all want a piece.
Except those punk asses. It's like they don't even want the win. They're just sitting there pouting.
I know they see me, but they won't even look up at me. It's so frickin' dramatic.
Just look at me, you jerks! Don't you get it? If we can't all work together, we don't stand a chance at winning.
Isn't that why we're here? To play at our very best?
Coach Nozomi, almost all of them are done. Bring in some of the second and third years.
What?
We can't make a play with this crap. Did you see them? Aoi, Kurara, and Asari? They're useless. Like they're drunk or sleepwalking.
And yeah, I realize I'm overstepping quite a bit. Forgive me, but I don't want us to lose here.
I agree with you. So act as if your life depends on it.
Hold on.
Togashi. For the second half, you'll go in for Ishiki at center back.
Coach, I don't think you really mean that. Why would you add Togashi to the mix when the goal is to clean up the mess?
I'm confused by it myself. I don't see how I can score three goals with these entitled pouty players.
They're more about protecting their elite status and cheap sense of pride over playing with real skill and winning.
Guess that's how it is when you're from the academy. Not much ever changes, I see.
Bastard! Say it one more time! Togashi!
That's not true, okay?
What?
I don't mean about us not being in sync. We weren't, and we aren't communicating. But something is happening, and you need to see it.
Everyone here is doing their best. None of us are stupid enough to put ourselves through all this if we didn't want to win.
Nothing matters more. We know that.
Clean up whatever's festering.
I'm not giving you any more matches. This is your only shot. There are 45 minutes left in the match.
Get comfortable with being uncomfortable out on the field. Hard work is exhausting.
If you all self-destruct, at least you'll know you gave it everything you had. Then you'll do training runs until summer.
Thank you.
What? Are you freaking kidding me? They've got four, five, six defenders back there. The halfbacks are mostly positioned as defenders as well. I never thought they'd dare fall back that much.
Well, they're focusing on defense, not appearances.
That's right! Let's finish this out! You're gonna crush them!
B-team? More like D-team!
Aoi, Kurada, Asari. What's going through your heads? Better figure it out quickly. If you guys don't get your useless line together, they'll bust through and we'll be screwed.
Huh? What is he talking about? Line? Why did only those two get so upset?
Wait a minute. Is that it? I did notice that the three of us were always playing on the same line. I don't remember any other players there. Was it a test?
What's happening? I don't feel right. Something is seriously strange here. But, what?
What an odd level of defense.
But it seems to be working out for them just fine. And it's not like they have anyone who can bust it open. Can't expect much else from a B-team.
What? Are you kidding me? I didn't touch him!
I suggest you watch your mouth, kid. Calm down. You're getting desperate and it shows. Keep it up and I'll give you a yellow card.
What's your deal? Anything to say? Aren't you embarrassed? Why are you playing scared defense?
We're getting bored. Wake up. Give us a challenge.
Hmm. Yeah, I agree it's not fun. But hey, you know why it's necessary?
Deal with it! We refuse to be defeated by a consolation prize team!
Hmm.
Say something, cause you look creepy.
I noticed something. You've been overlapping. And you're incredible. Like, you're a master at it.
Hmm?
You've always been a defender, haven't you? I just saw you come back from the keeper's area. Holy crap, I'm right! Whenever I look back, I always see you behind me somehow.
Hmm.
Hey! Everyone come back!
And... and Kurada, he does it too.
I see it. He always positions himself between me and Asuri. Hey guys, what's up?
Why don't you tell me? Were you leisurely watching your teammates this whole time? We only have 30 minutes!
I see it! Notice right away! As soon as I paid attention, I knew what they were doing! It's obvious!
Well, it should be. All three of you are sharing the same line. It doesn't take a genius to notice your surroundings.
No, that's not it! Not all of it! But even if it was...
Uh...
Think you can act human for at least 15 minutes?
I don't know, to be honest. I'm weirded out.
Huh?
This entire time, I've been thinking...
Why aren't they getting the play that I'm trying to make?
What am I doing wrong?
Why are they doing their best to ignore me out here?
But now...
I see that I was the one ignoring what was right in front of my eyes!
Was it me? Was I the source of the problem?
Hey, Nozomi, let's swish him out.
If we don't, it could affect the morale in the future.
I feel like we especially need to call back Aoi and Asari.
Five more minutes.
I need a little more time to watch them.
Asari! Returning to center! It's surrounding you! Asari!
That's right. Distance.
The three of us tend to be within proximity of each other most of the time.
If I take the ball and run with it, without ever looking around, they usually try to catch up with me.
But still, I can't quite make sense of what that means yet.
Okay. So, Kuroda is over there right now. And I'm out here, but...
If I were in Asari's place, where would I most want me to be?
Whoa! It went through!
Hey, Aoi! Go cover!
Yeah! Goal kick!
Too bad, you team! You finally got through and nobody cares!
Don't get used to it! You got lucky!
Oh!
Hey, Owie! Go cover!
Yeah! Goal kick!
Aw, too bad, youth team.
You finally got through, and nobody cares!
Don't get used to it! You got lucky!
Another classic Owie moment.
The ball had gone through nice and clean,
but he just stood there staring at it, doing nothing.
He performed like this all day,
and it's already been five minutes.
Let's pull him.
I'm more disappointed in your performance.
You're always saying to think outside the theory,
but I can see it never really applied to you.
You say you're a hardcore Fukuda fanatic,
but you're clearly rattled by our opponents being up by three goals.
We have thirty more minutes to go.
Plenty of time.
I'm still expecting something exciting to happen.
Maybe you should expect the same.
I can't believe it.
I actually got my hopes up for you again.
Nice move on the defensive positioning,
and a one-touch pass to Fukuda was brilliant.
I fell for it.
But then you couldn't be bothered to go into cover.
You obviously still don't get what this game's about.
Stupid.
I don't know how a noob like you ended up on Asperion
when you clearly don't know what you're doing.
You won't be able to fake it forever.
Oh?
Asuri!
The three of them are interesting to watch.
Those three that play the left wing?
Oh, come on!
You ladies just gonna keep passing the ball between the three of you?
Why are you wasting time when we're up three on you?
Oh, I get it.
So one of those players is actually your boyfriend, is that right?
If it's the cute one with the blonde hair, you're my new hero!
Not even close, but it's hard to explain.
Something's changed between those three,
and it happened so quickly.
Sorry, Kurada.
I suck.
I was so obsessed with how stupid Asuri was feeling,
I completely tuned you out.
Pass the ball,
and then immediately go to cover the receiver.
Do I have that right?
You're passing the ball to him again?
So if I were Kurada,
where would I position myself?
Ashito! Go to the other side!
Ashito! Behind you! Pass it back!
I'm sorry, you guys. I can't this time.
I have to trust and focus on what Asuri and Kurada are doing.
I don't know why. I can't explain it.
But there's a loud voice in my head telling me this is what I have to do.
Oh. Okay. I see it now.
Those three players keep looking at each other.
Which means they're communicating strategy with their eyes.
Take the shot, Aoi!
I can do a middle range shot right now!
No!
Way to go, guys!
That's how you break them up, Aoi! Brilliant!
One goal down!
Hey, I'm not worried about it.
We're still up by two goals!
Fifteen more minutes!
Keep it up and we win!
Not worried? I don't know about that.
I gotta admit, I didn't even see it coming.
There's so many of us on defense.
Yet they managed to break us up effortlessly.
There are only three of them.
Gotta get going! Move!
That was your shot.
Why did you pass the ball to me?
I'm not sure myself.
Hmm.
He was right. That was my shot.
I didn't even realize I was doing it.
I passed the ball to Asuri.
Normally, I would have gone for the goal myself. No question.
But I couldn't.
I didn't want to compromise my pride as a forward.
So then, why did I?
Uh-huh?
That's right.
Help me!
Teach me how to play soccer!
Your way!
You came here to make a change in yourself, didn't you?
I get it! It's finally happening!
I'm learning how to play soccer!
Ashito!
Watch out! They're coming in from the side!
You know, you were right.
Something interesting is happening with those three fellas.
They're making eye contact.
Like constantly looking back and forth at each other.
Trying to communicate.
In sports like soccer, where the situations can change,
you don't have the time or space to yell out instructions to your teammates.
In which case, the most effective method is...
using eye contact.
When Oof Tanz became the general manager for the national team,
he made sure to ingrain the most basic of basics into his players.
And yet, even today's top players haven't been able to master it.
Magic just doesn't happen by glancing at each other.
Huh?
There needs to be a mutual understanding between the players.
And if that's the case here,
then I'd say those three have an ideal relationship.
Asuri! I need you to run in!
Okay!
Oh no you don't!
It's all coming to me now.
Three!
That's the number that really matters out here.
Not one, or two, but three.
Soccer is a sport where you need three teammates to carry the ball forward together.
The most intriguing part for me is...
What happened to make them bond so suddenly?
This is so exciting!
Takurada!
No matter how tight the defense might be,
when three people who share the same mind go at it,
they will create a gap!
Yeah!
Ha ha!
Huh?
Oh!
Thank you.
Next time on Awashi, Eagle Eye.